What's up, guys?
>> What's up, Jackson?
>> How you doing?
>> Good, man.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Rock wall, Texas. Yes, sir.
>> Got to learn from
>> IO.
>> Did your research?
>> I like that.
What do you have to say?
>> Man, you got to have faith. You got to
believe in God. You got to give it to
him. And you know, you're going to get
battle tested. You're going to there's
going to be ups, there's going to be
downs, but you have to nobody can move
you. Nobody can change you. You have to
believe in what you believe in and stand
tall on that. and never waver and
you know have faith man have faith your
faith has to be there and and it's been
a blessing and you know everybody a part
of your journey is
[clears throat] it's just everything
everything is everything and you know
when bad things happen good things
happen you got to use that you got to
use that to be a world champ and you got
to believe that you're a world champ
before you're a world champ and it's
amazing Thank you so much.
>> IO.
>> It's great, man. Jesus Jesus is
everything. And you know, when I put
when I put it on his shoulders, you
know, he takes he takes it off my
shoulders. And you know, he never fails
me. He's never failed me. Um whether we
would have won or lost today, you know,
Jesus won and I'm just happy to give him
the glory today.
>> Seahawk tattoo. Why not? You know, I got
some space left. So, I'm definitely
going to
>> next to it. I I don't got no space on my
right arm, but you know, maybe my left
arm. [laughter]
[gasps]
>> Man, I'm on cloud nine. I ain't gonna
lie. I'm straight though.
>> Jackson, you're a big bad fan. Did you
get a chance to try to slip over the
halftime at all?
>> No, I didn't. I wish I did though. I
told everybody that I was going to go
out there and sneak out and and watch
him, but I didn't get a chance to.
>> What' you learn about?
>> Sam Donald, he's a beast. He's
everything that you want in a
quarterback and a leader. You know, he
led his troops today like he's been
doing all season. He doesn't let the
noise get to him.
Um,
you know, he's a baller, man. And I've
been saying it. I've been saying it. You
know, the media, they got their own. You
know, they want to, you know, they want
to talk about some, but he's a world
champ and that's something you can't
take from them. And that's something
that Semen in history.
>> Jason, you obviously have a heavy
workload throughout the season. How
great was it to see other guys step up,
>> man? They've been doing that all season.
They've been doing that all season. And
however we got to win, we find a way to
win. You know, there's been games I
caught two balls. I don't know what I
had tonight, but there's been games I
caught two balls and we win, you know.
Um, so it's just amazing to go out there
with these group of guys and and know
that, you know what, we're going to do
whatever it takes to win. And that's the
vibe I'm on for sure.
>> What up, buddy?
>> What's up, dog? Thank you, brother.
Yeah.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Honestly, I didn't know when I got
drafted, but the Seahawks and what in
the 12s what they bring, they bring it's
something special. They're the best fans
in the world and I'm happy that the
world get to see it and um you know
we've used their energy
all year long and
you know we're just ready to keep this
thing rolling.
>> Yes sir.
>> Jackson Smith and Jake but put respect
on it. You heard me. Um, you know, Sier
Sierra Leon Salone. Um, you know, my
grandfather came to the United States in
the 70s. Um, had to work for everything
that he had. Um, you know, brought a lot
of people over here, brought a lot of
family over here, and he was a leader
and, you know, um, took pride in who he
was and and what he had to give back to.
and I represent I represent him. I
represent my family. I represent Sierra
Leon Bo Freetown. Um, you know, it's an
honor just to even say that. I
appreciate you asking that question.
It's an honor to say that up here in
front of y'all. Um, and I and I take
great pride in it.
>> How tough was the match up against?
[clears throat]
>> Honestly, I felt like we had our way.
You know, we didn't score in the red
zone, but I felt like we had our way. We
we drove the ball down. And I thought
K9, man, I'm so happy for him, man.
Y'all don't understand what K9 has gone
through. And you know, you know, just
he's a special player. He's a special
player in our in our O line. They're
special. You know, we have a special
group of guys. And I feel like when you
look back at this team, y'all will
realize, you know, how special we are.
>> One more time.
>> Oh, yeah. Oh, man. and they're the best
in the world. Defense wins
championships. We're not here without
our defense. From from the front line to
the back line, those guys,
man, are special and we we sharpen our
tools with them um in the offseason and
they got us better. And we're not here
without our defense, man. The real dark
side. [__] get dark. Like for real. Like
[laughter]
>> for real.
>> For real. I'm sorry, guys. I had fun.
>> Peace.
>> Offseason. Oh, a whole I want to get
better. Yes, sir. Peace.